ELIAS LUNA

ELUNAJ.GITHUB.IO | GITHUB.COM/ELUNAJ | LINKEDIN.COM/IN/ELIASLUNA23/ ELIASLUNAJ@GMAIL.COM | (917)-526-9488

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Soon-to-be new grad transitioning from a freelance career in seasonal film festivals/events to software engineering. Passion for web development and learning new technologies. Experience in leading projects, managing employees, and working effectively within a team.

SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript (Node, Express, React), Java (JSP, Servlets, Spring Boot), SQL (Postgres, MySQL)

Technologies: HTML / CSS, Git/GitHub, Redis, Postman, Logic Pro X, Heroku

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

CUNY Tech Prep

Software Student Developer

New York, NY Jun 2019 – Present

- Selected for a full-stack Javascript training program (125 selected from 400+ applicants)
- Gained familiarity with React, Node + Express, Postgres, Git/GitHub, industry best practices
- Learned Agile methodologies (Scrum in Trello and Slack)
- Experienced test-driven development and setting up CI/CD pipelines

Image-Crawl - https://image-crawl.herokuapp.com/

Mar 2020 - Apr 2020

- Developed a web crawler that downloads all images from a given website
- Implemented RESTful API endpoints for webpage crawl and image download
- Added a cache to improve web crawler performance and prevent IP ban
- Technologies: React, Material UI, Spring Boot, Redis, Jsoup, Heroku

Samplfi - https://samplfi.herokuapp.com/

Feb 2020

- · Created a web app that performs a basic analysis (such as beats per minute) of any song in the Spotify catalog
- Added a feature that lets registered users create a music track collection
- Designed CRUD routes to process user requests
- Technologies: React, Material UI, Node, Express, Bcrypt, Axios, Knex, Postgres, Spotify Web API, Heroku

Global-Port - https://github.com/elunaj/Global-Port

Aug 2019 - Dec 2019

- · With a team of 4 at CUNY Tech Prep, created a social media platform for soon-to-be travelers
- · Utilized the Leaflet JavaScript library to embed an interactive user map on each registered user's homepage
- · Helped design and implement an in-app chat feature
- Technologies: React, Bootstrap, Node, Express, Sequelize, Postgres, Passport, Leaflet, ipapi, Chatkit API

EDUCATION

City University of New York (CUNY) - New York City College of Technology (NYCCT)

Brooklyn, NY

BTech in Computer Systems Technology (Software Development Specialization) | GPA: 3.89 / 4.00 Expected: May 2020

- Achievements: Dean's List (2018, 2019)
- Selected Coursework: Discrete Structures & Algorithms, Data Structures, Object-Oriented Programming, Object-Oriented Design, Web Development, Database Design, Operating Systems, Networking, Computer Security

WORK EXPERIENCE - VARIOUS FILM FESTIVALS AND EVENTS | 2012 - 2018

 Managed, trained, and supervised box office personnel, installed and troubleshot ticket printing and scanning systems, managed general theater operations, assisted senior staff with logistics and database management, VIP and customer relations